<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">LoginRegister01</string>
    <string name="otpverification">otpVerification</string>
    <string name="otp_verification">otp_verification</string>
    <string name="we_will_send_you_a_one_time_password_on_this_mobile_number">we will send you a one time password on this mobile number</string>
    <string name="We_will_send_you_a_one_time_password_on_this_mobile_number">We_will_send_you_a_one_time_password_on_this_mobile_number</string>
    <string name="enter_mobile_number">Enter Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="otpVerification">otp Verification</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="please_login_to_your_account">Please Login to your account</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign In with Google</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="create_a_new_account">Create a new account</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="_254">+254</string>
    <string name="_0712345678">0712345678</string>
    <string name="get_otp">Get OTP</string>
    <string name="no">_</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="did_not_receive_otp">Did not receive OTP?</string>
    <string name="resend_code">Resend Code</string>
    <string name="_254_0723963795">+254–0723963795</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="test_gmail_com">test@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="please_enter_the_verification_code">Please enter the verification code</string>
    <string name="_07">07</string>
    <string name="_254n">+254-</string>
    <string name="_0700000000">0700000000</string>
    <string name="_0723963795">0723963795</string>
    <string name="pamoja_prep">Pamoja prep</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="please_verify_the_email_sent_to">Please verify the email sent to</string>
    <string name="check_your_phone_for_the_code_sent_to">Check your phone for the code sent to</string>
    <string name="term_of_service">Term of Service</string>

    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="last_update_june_1_2023">Last update June 1 2023</string>
    <string name="googlebtn">googleBtn</string>
    <string name="i_have_read_the_terms_and_conditions">I have read the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="please_re_type_the_password">Please re-type the password</string>
    <string name="password_should_be">Password should be</string>
    <string name="at_least_one_uppercase">At least one Uppercase</string>
    <string name="at_least_one_lowercase">At least one Lowercase</string>
    <string name="at_least_one_number">At least one Number</string>
    <string name="at_least_one_special_character">At least one Special character</string>
    <string name="minimum_8_characters">Minimum 8 characters</string>
    <string name="please_enter_valid_email">Please enter valid email</string>
    <string name="please_enter_a_valid_mobile_number">Please enter a valid mobile number</string>
    <string name="please_enter_full_name">Please enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="please_enter_password">Please enter password</string>
    <string name="i_am_over_18_years">I am over 18 years</string>
    <string name="i_have_read_and_agreed_to_the_terms_and_conditions">I have read and agreed to the terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms And Conditions</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="at_least_one_symbol" />
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming Soon...</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="geography">Geography</string>
    <string name="chemistry">Chemistry</string>
    <string name="physics">Physics</string>
    <string name="biology">Biology</string>
    <string name="elements_in_our_day_to_day">Elements in our day to day</string>
    <string name="mathematics">Mathematics</string>
    <string name="transforming_academics_at_your_your_finger_tips">Transforming academics at your your finger tips.</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer </string>
    <string name="close_nav"> Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"
        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="firebase_terms">
        Firebase Data_Processing_and_Security_Terms.

        bookmark_border last modified: June 1, 2023 | Previous versions
        The customer agreeing to these terms ("Customer"), and Google LLC
        (formerly known as Google Inc.),
        Google Ireland Limited, Google Asia Pacific Pte. Ltd., or any other entity that directly
        or
       indirectly controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with Google LLC.
        (as applicable, "Google"), have entered into an agreement under which Google has agreed
        to
        provide Firebase Services (as described at https://firebase.google.com/terms) which
        specifically reference the Firebase Data Processing and Security Terms
        (as amended from time to time, the "Agreement").

        These Firebase Data Processing and Security Terms.\n\n"

        Including their appendices,(the "Terms") are incorporated into the Agreement.
        These Terms will be effective and.
        replace any previously applicable data processing and security terms as from the Terms
        Effective Date (as defined below). ​ With respect to the Firebase Crashlytics and
        Firebase App Distribution Terms of Service under which Google has agreed to provide
        Firebase Crashlytics and Firebase App Distribution Services, these Terms were formerly
        known as the "Crashlytics and App Distribution Data Processing and Security Terms.

        "1. Introduction.\n\n\"

        "These Terms reflect the parties \\ agreement with respect to the terms governing the"
        "processing and security of Customer Data under the Agreement.\n"
        "2. Definitions2.1 Capitalized terms used but not defined in these Terms have the"
        "meanings set out in the Agreement. In these Terms, unless stated otherwise:"
        "Account has the meaning given in the Agreement or, if no such meaning is given, means"
        "Customer\'s account for the Services.Additional Product means a product,"
        "service or application provided by Google or a third party that:"
        "(a) is not part of the Services; and"
        "(b) is accessible for use within the user.\n"
        interface of the Services or is otherwise integrated with the Services.
        Additional Security Controls means security resources, features, functionality
        and/or controls
        that Customer may use at its option and/or as it determines, including the Admin Console
        and other features and/or functionality of the Services such as logging and monitoring
        and identity and access management.
        Adequate Country means:
        (a) for data processed subject to the EU GDPR: the EEA, or a country or territory recognized
        as ensuring adequate data protection under the EU GDPR;
        (b) for data processed subject to the UK GDPR: the UK or a country or territory recognized as
        ensuring adequate data protection under the UK GDPR and the Data Protection Act 2018;
        and/or

        "© for data processed subject to the Swiss FDPA:.\n\n"

        Switzerland, or a country or territory that is
        (i) included in the list of the states whose legislation ensures adequate protection as
        published by the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, or
        (ii) recognized as ensuring adequate data protection under the Swiss FDPA,
        in each case, other than on the basis of an optional data protection framework.
        Admin Console has the meaning given in the Agreement or, if no such meaning is given,
        means the online console(s) and/or tool(s) provided by Google to Customer for
        administering the Services.Affiliate has the meaning given in the Agreement or,
        if no such meaning is given, means any entity that directly or indirectly controls,
        is controlled by, or is under common control with, a party.
        Alternative Transfer Solution means a solution, other than SCCs, that enables the lawful
        transfer of personal data to a third country in accordance with European Data
        Protection Law, for example a data protection framework recognized as ensuring that
        participating local entities provide adequate protection.Audited Services means
        the then-current Services indicated as being in-scope for the relevant
        certification or report at https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/#certifications,
        as may be updated by Google from time to time.
        Customer Data has the meaning given in the Agreement or, if no such meaning is given, has the
        meaning given to "Developer Data" in the Agreement, or if no such meaning is given, means
        data provided by or on behalf of Customer or Customer End Users via the Services
        (except TSS and any other support services, if applicable) under the Account.
        Customer End Users means the individuals who are permitted by Customer to use the Services.
        For clarity, Customer End Users may include employees of Customer Affiliates and other
        authorized third parties.Customer Personal Data means the personal data contained
        within the Customer Data, including anyspecial categories of personal data defined under
        European Data Protection Law.Customer SCCs means the SCCs (Controller-to-Processor),
        the SCCs (Processor-to-Processor), and/or the SCCs (Processor-to-Controller), as applicable.

        "Data Incident.\n\n"

        means a breach of Google\'s security leading to the accidental or unlawful
        destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to,
        Customer Data on systems managed by or otherwise controlled by Google.
        European Data Protection Law means, as applicable: (a) the GDPR; and/or (b) the Swiss FDPA.
        EEA means the European Economic Area.EU GDPR means Regulation
        (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April
        2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data
        and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.

        European Law means, as applicable: (a) EU or EU Member State law (if the EU GDPR applies to the
        processing of Customer Personal Data); and (b) the law of the UK or a part of the UK
        (if the UK GDPR applies to the processing of Customer Personal Data).

        GDPR means, as applicable: (a) the EU GDPR; and/or (b) the UK GDPR.

        Google\'s Third Party Auditor means a Google-appointed, qualified and independent third party
        auditor, whose then-current identity Google will disclose to Customer.

        Instructions has the meaning given in Section 5.2.1 (Customer’s Instructions).

        ISO 27001 Certification means an ISO/IEC 27001:2013 certification or a comparable certification
        for the Audited Services.

        Non-European Data Protection Law means data protection or privacy laws in force outside the EEA,
        Switzerland, and the UK.
        U.S. State Privacy Laws Addendum at terms/usa-privacy-addendum"
    </string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_last_name">Please enter your Last name!</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_first_name">Please enter your first name!</string>
    <string name="verification_link_sent_to">Verification link sent to:</string>
    <string name="a">A:</string>
    <string name="q1">Q1:</string>
    <string name="_5_numbers">5.Numbers</string>
    <string name="_4_measurement">4.Measurement</string>
    <string name="_3_geometry">3.Geometry</string>
    <string name="_2_data_handling">2.Data Handling</string>
    <string name="_1_algebra">1.Algebra</string>
    <string name="topics">Topics:</string>
    <string name="b">B:</string>
    <string name="c">C:</string>
    <string name="d">D:</string>
    <string name="correct_answer">Correct Answer:</string>
    <string name="q2">Q2:</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="enter_your_feedback">Enter your feedback...</string>
    <string name="profile_picture_description" />
    <string name="dark_mode" />
    <string name="first_name">First name</string>
</resources>